I break the Islamization of the West. I
break it up in four phases. Four phases.
Phase one, open borders and immigration.
They the Muslims play the victim card.
They say we need help. Uh you start to
see halal food promoted everywhere. Oh
my listeners, you've seen halal food
everywhere. Like yeah, it's so nice. No,
that's phase one of Islamizing the West.
You start to see a lot more hijabs. Uh
you start to see a lot more moss built.
That's phase one. It's a lot easy. Very
peaceful, very kind people. Phase two,
and this is America's there. Muslims
begin to gather in large groups of
people, which is happening New York Time
Square.
>> You guys have seen it.
>> Time Square, New York, thousands of
Muslims. That's phase two. They They're
no longer in one or two or five. Now
they're in the thousands. They come,
they begin to pray in the streets
publicly. Michigan, they're not praying
in a in a mosque anymore. They begin to
pray in the street showing dominance.
They begin to infiltrate politics like
Zohani. This is phase two. They begin to
open prayer rooms for for Muslims in and
they did it in the Vatican. They just
opened a Muslim prayer room. They begin
to open prayer rooms. Then phase three.
Phase three is where Michigan is at
right now. Isaiah, Michigan is at phase
three. And New York will be in phase
three very soon. What's phase three?
They begin to get the call to prayer in
the in in the street.
>> Insane, dude.
>> The call to prayer. So, so, so now no
longer no longer is is is is the the the
music and the Quran and the prayer in
the mosque. It's now facing outside.
Michigan, you hear five times a day
Allah Akbar. You start to see rape cases
increase. Rape cases. This is what
happened in the UK. Phase three, rape
will go up. That's just a fact. Islam is
a sexually perverted religion. It is a
sexually perverted religion. You know
why? By the way, Isaiah, you you know
you and all my listeners, you know why
the the rape cases are so high? When
Muslims migrate to the west, the rape
cases are so high. A few reasons. Number
one, in Muslim countries, women are not
allowed to show their skin.
>> The women cover their cover their whole
body from head to toe. In Afghanistan,
the Taliban told the woman, you have to
cover your eyes. They It's like a ninja.
They can't speak or sing in public. So,
so number one, the men have never seen a
woman before. They've never seen her
skin. Number two, which is a crazy one,
is in Islam, heaven is a brothel. So for
men, Muslim men, the reward in heaven is
72 virgins.
>> So what's our reward? Our reward is
Jesus Christ. Our reward is to be in the
presence of God, to worship the Lord
Jesus Christ with all the angels and all
of creation and all the believers. Their
reward is 72 virgins. So now you have a
Muslim man who's never seen a naked
woman, but he he's imagining naked women
in heaven in heaven cuz the Quran by the
way and the hadith you I'm not going to
say it on this podcast but the hadith is
disgusting. It is pornography.